Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2010
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer Roger Reynolds with conductor James Baker and violinist Irvine Arditti at rehearsal of Reynolds's work, Aspiration, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Roger Reynolds speaking with violinist soloist Irvi.tif (Image-file JIB2010_077)
- Composer Roger Reynolds at rehearsal of his work, Aspiration with conductor James Baker, violinist Irvine Arditti, and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Roger Reynolds composer speaking to violinist soloist Irvine.tif (Image-file JIB2010_078)
- Composer Roger Reynolds with conductor James Baker and violinist Irvine Arditti at rehearsal of Reynolds's work, Aspiration, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Roger Reynolds speaking to violinist Irvine Arditti.tif (Image-file JIB2010_079)
- Composer Roger Reynolds with conductor James Baker and violinist Irvine Arditti at rehearsal of Reynolds's work, Aspiration, at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer_Roger_Reynolds...[too long to state].tif (Image-file JIB2010_080)
- Composer Roger Reynolds at rehearsal of his work, Aspiration with conductor James Baker, violinist Irvine Arditti, and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Roger Reynolds with violinist soloist Irvine Arditti and com.tif (Image-file JIB2010_081)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor rehearsing David Felder's work, Tweener at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Tom Kolor percussion soloist in David Felder Tweener June in.tif (Image-file JIB2010_082)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor rehearsing David Felder's work, Tweener at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: percussion soloist Tom Kolor in David Felder Tweener June in.tif (Image-file JIB2010_083)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet at computer at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Olivier Pasquet in June in Buffalo at Lippes Concer.tif (Image-file JIB2010_084)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet's computers before performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Olivier Pasquet's computer.tif (Image-file JIB2010_085)
- James Baker conducting percussionist Tom Kolor and the Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's work, Tweener at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo James Baker conducting Slee Sinfonietta at L.tif (Image-file JIB2010_086)
- Composer David Felder shaking hands with conductor James Baker after a performance of Felder's Tweener by percussionist Tom Kolor and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer David Felder shaking hands with conducter James Bak.tif (Image-file JIB2010_087)
- David Felder on stage with Slee Sinfonietta after performance of his composition, Tweener, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: after David Felder performance of Tweener with conductor Jam.tif (Image-file JIB2010_088)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti taking a bow onstage with conductor James Baker, composer Roger Reynolds (mostly hidden), and the Slee Sinfonietta after a performance of Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: violinist soloist Irvine Arditti taking a bow after performi.tif (Image-file JIB2010_089)
- Student composer Daniel Bassin speaking with Lucas Fels, violoncellist with the Arditti Quartet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composer Daniel Bassin Lucas Fels, cello at Arditti.tif (Image-file JIB2010_090)
- Student composer Daniel Bassin speaking with violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composer Daniel Bassin speaking to Irvin Arditti, v.tif (Image-file JIB2010_091)
- Composer David Felder speaking with members of the Arditti Quartet during a workshop performance of Daniel Bassin's Typographies II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Dr. David Felder speaking to Arditti Quartet at Wor.tif (Image-file JIB2010_092)
- Composer David Felder applauding the Arditti Quartet at workshop performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 040.tif (Image-file JIB2010_093)
- Composer David Felder applauding the Arditti Quartet at workshop performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 043.tif (Image-file JIB2010_094)
- Arditti String Quartet in workshop performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Arditti Workshop June in Buffalo Irvin Arditti, violin Ashot.tif (Image-file JIB2010_095)
- Arditti String Quartet in workshop performance of student composer Daniel Bassin's work, Typographies II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Arditti Quartet at Workshop June in Buffalo Baird H.tif (Image-file JIB2010_096)
- Arditti String Quartet in workshop performance of student composer Daniel Bassin's Typographies II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 011.tif (Image-file JIB2010_097)
- Arditti String Quartet in workshop performance of student composer Daniel Bassin's work, Typographies II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop with student composers Arditti Quartet at June in B.tif (Image-file JIB2010_098)
- Arditti String Quartet in workshop performance of student composer Daniel Bassin's Typographies II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 015.tif (Image-file JIB2010_099)
- Student composer Daniel Bassin speaking with Ashot Sarkissjan, violinist with the Arditti Quartet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composer Daniel Bassin speaking to Ralf Ehlers, viol.tif (Image-file JIB2010_100)
- Student composers Chun Ting Pang, Daniel Bassin, and Carl Christian Bettendorf at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 student composers Daniel Bassin, Carl C.tif (Image-file JIB2010_101)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas, conductor Brad Lubman, and violinist Yuki Numata at rehearsal of Thomas's work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 041.tif (Image-file JIB2010_102)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas, conductor Brad Lubman, and violinist Yuki Numata at rehearsal of Thomas's work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 048.tif (Image-file JIB2010_103)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas, conductor Brad Lubman, and violinist Yuki Numata at rehearsal of Thomas's work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 066.tif (Image-file JIB2010_104)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 076.tif (Image-file JIB2010_105)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 083.tif (Image-file JIB2010_106)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 083====.tif (Image-file JIB2010_107)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 084.tif (Image-file JIB2010_108)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 084===.tif (Image-file JIB2010_109)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal of her work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 088.tif (Image-file JIB2010_110)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Yuki Numata at rehearsal of Augusta Read Thomas's work, Carillon Sky, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 089.tif (Image-file JIB2010_111)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet during lecture presentation at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Olivier Pasquet looking at his rythem dots.tif (Image-file JIB2010_112)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet during lecture presentation at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Olivier Pasquet reading his score.tif (Image-file JIB2010_113)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet during lecture presentation at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: -Oliver Pasquet.tif (Image-file JIB2010_114)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet during lecture presentation at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-03, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Oliver Pasquet looking at his rhythm dots=.tif (Image-file JIB2010_115)
- Conductor Brad Lubman conferring with composer Bernard Rands at rehearsal of Rands's work, Now again -- fragments from Sappho, at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 008.tif (Image-file JIB2010_116)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet talking with student composers Daniel Bassin, Jordan Kuspa, Mischa Salkind-Pearl, and Ashley Wang at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composers Daniel Bassin, Jordan Kuspa, Misha Salkind.tif (Image-file JIB2010_117)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet during workshop at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop with Olivier Pasquet.tif (Image-file JIB2010_118)
- Composer Bernard Rands with conductor Brad Lubman and mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley at rehearsal with Slee Sinfonietta of Rands's work, Now again -- fragments from Sappho at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 028.tif (Image-file JIB2010_119)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and conductor Brad Lubman examining score of Bernard Rands's work, Now again -- fragments from Sappho at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 030.tif (Image-file JIB2010_120)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger performing his work, New Millennium Memo at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Harvey Sollenberger playing his New Mellwnnium Memo at the A.tif (Image-file JIB2010_121)
- Brad Lubman conducting violinist Yuki Numata and the Slee Sinfonietta in performance of Augusta Read Thomas's work, Carillon Sky at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: violin soloist Yuky Numata playing Augusta Read Thomas Caril.tif (Image-file JIB2010_122)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas, violin soloist Yuki Numata, conductor Brad Lubman, and the Slee Sinfonietta after a performance of Thomas's Carillon Sky at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Augusta Read Thomas with violin soloist Yuki Namuta.tif (Image-file JIB2010_123)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas, violin soloist Yuki Numata, conductor Brad Lubman, and the Slee Sinfonietta after a performance of Thomas's Carillon Sky at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 014.tif (Image-file JIB2010_124)
- Composer David Felder with brass quintet on stage after performance of Felder's Canzonne XXXI at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Dr.David Felder and brass ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_125)
- Brass quintet of Adam Unsworth, Benjamin Herrington, Jim Daniels, Tim Leopold, and Jon Nelson performing David Felder's work, Canzonne XXXI at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: playing composer David Felder CANZONNE.tif (Image-file JIB2010_126)
- Composer David Felder applauding performers after a performance of his Canzonne XXXI at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer David Felder applauding brass ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_127)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley performing Bernard Rands's work, Now again -- fragments from Sappho with Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Julia Bentley, mezzo soprano performing Now again-fragments .tif (Image-file JIB2010_128)
- Composer Bernard Rands with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, conductor Brad Lubman, and members of the Slee Sinfonietta after a performance of Rands's Now again -- fragments from Sappho at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Bernard Rands, mezzo soprano Julia Bentley and cond.tif (Image-file JIB2010_129)
- Composer Bernard Rands onstage with mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, conductor Brad Lubman, and the Slee Sinfonietta after a performance of Rands's work, Now again -- fragments from Sappho at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-04, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: mezzo soprano Julia Bentley, composer Bernard Rands, Brad L.tif (Image-file JIB2010_130)
- Student composers Felipe Ribeiro, John Bacon, and Ethan Hayden testing sounds at the piano at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 051.tif (Image-file JIB2010_131)
- Student composers Ashley Wang, Huck Hodge, and others in workshop at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-05, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Student Forum with student composer Ashely Wang, Huck Hodge .tif (Image-file JIB2010_132)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta rehearsing with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Buffalo Philharmonic June In Buffalo June 6 005.tif (Image-file JIB2010_133)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta rehearsing with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-06, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Buffalo Philharmonic June In Buffalo June 6 008.tif (Image-file JIB2010_134)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.